

# **AHMED ABBASSI**

#### **Software Engineering Student**

- @ a.abbassi21306@pi.tn
- **J** +216 23-631-633
- Tunis, Tunisia

- in ahmed-abbassi-
- 3ibsi69

#### **SKILLS**



JavaScript Python

Microsoft Word SQL

Microsoft Excel | PLSQL

LateX

Linux

## **CERTIFICATION**

Microsoft Word (office 2016)

Microsoft Excel (office 2016)

# **LANGUAGES**

Arabic: Native

English: Intermediate / B2

French: Intermediate / B1

# **INTERESTS**

Gaming Music Sports

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a 21 years old student seeking opportunities to apply my knowledge and skills in a real-world setting, and eager to contribute to innovative projects that make a positive impact. I hope to bring the best out of myself and work within a well-communicated team.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Part-time Sales Associate | Decathlon

iii 10/06/2023 - Present

Tunis, Tunisia

Internship | Karriery

29/05/2023 - Present

Tunis, Tunisia

Internship | B and smile

**1** 01/08/2022 - 31/08/2022

Tunis, Tunisia

### **EDUCATION**

Software Engineering | Polytech INTL

**1** 09 2021 - Present

Tunis, Tunisia

Computer Science Baccalaureate | Rue de Russie High School

**i** 09 2020 - 05 2021

Tunis, Tunisia

### **PROJECTS**

Portfolio Website 😱

- **=** 05/06/2023 08/06/2023
- HTML CSS SCSS JavaScript

Clinic site for booking 🕠

- **\*\*** 02/02/2023 03/16/2023
- HTML CSS Javascript Php

To Do-list 🖸

- **1**2/06/2023
- HTML CSS Javascript

Search tool 🖸

- **=** 05/01/2023 05/09/2023
- Python

Gestion de stock

- **1** 01-2022 02-2022
- | C